《金斯敦市长》前情提要
Previously on Mayor of Kingstown...
麦洛打破了秩序
Milo broke something.
他擅自妄为 扰乱秩序
He took it and he broke it.
所以咱们不能放他走
And that's why we're not letting him leave.
但你必须让这事顺其自然
But you have to let shit play out.
邦尼 我们快成功了
Bunny, we're this fucking close.
我会把你从这里弄出去
I'm gonna get you out of here.
我等不了了 麦克
I can't bide my time, Mike.
按计划行事
Just stay the course.
我唯一知道的计划就是我自己的计划
Theonly course I see is the one I'm making.
搞什么
What the fuck?
我们有个囚犯 带他去了医务室
We had an inmate, took him to the infirmary,
医生们会给他做个体检 他们就会发现他从头到脚全是伤
docs examining him, they're gonna find a ton of trauma.
就不能有话直说吗 卡尼
Just be plain, Carney.
-他是那三个人之一  -哪三个人
- He's one of the three. - Three what?
嘿 他没有反抗狱警
Hey! He wasn't fucking resisting CO!
还跟我玩公民自由权 卡尼
You with the ACLU, Carney?
你自己待会儿吧 孙子
Get you some alone time, son.
他们把邦尼狠狠揍了一顿 麦克 还把他关进了单间
They put a beatdown on him, Mike and drug his ass to solitary.
我听说过你所有的事 白人救世主的屁话
I heard all about you. White savior bullshit.
你什么都拯救不了
You ain[t savin' shit.
你难道不觉得如果麦克·麦克拉斯基能解决这事
What, you think if Mike McLusky could fix this,
他现在应该已经解决了吗
he would have fixed it by now?
他们让劳改犯
They're farming out inmate labor to companies
为全州各地的公司工作
all across the state.
知道他们给多少报酬吗 每小时0.16美元
Know what they're paying? $0.16 an hour.
沃里克集团
这不就是打白工吗
That's fucking free labor.
他们给警犬买食物的钱
They're spending more money on food for guard dogs
都比花在犯人身上的钱多
than they are for the inmates.
他们没有出路
There's no way out for them.
你们也不想提供出路
And you don't want there to be.
你们要的就是这种闭环
You need that cycle,
这样才能从中赚钱
that's how you get paid.
这就是你大老远过来的来意吗 麦克
Is that why you came all the way up here, Mike?
跟我解释我们公司运转的机制
To explain to me how my company works?
我们试过所有方法 这就是我们最终的选择
It's all been tried, and this is where we've landed.
你可以参与进来
So you can join in,
或等着被前进的车轮碾压
or you can get crushed by the wheels of progress.
是吗 好吧
Yeah. Well...
我需要帮助
I need a favor.
是吗
Is that so?
最近在尽力完成一件事
Trying to get something done.
我试遍了各种方法 累了
I'm tired of the trees that I'm barking up.
所以想让你和你们前进的车轮
So you and your wheels of progress
帮我推进一下
can help me move something along.
那我能得到什么呢
And what do I get?
你能得到我
You get me.
我欠你个人情
I'll owe you something.
我有个伙计关在锚湾监狱
So I have a guy at Anchor Bay.
你想把他转到沃里克监狱吗
And you want him moved to Warwick?
不 当然不是 我想让他出来
No. Fuck, no. I want him out.
我跟地方检察官办公室做了交易
I have a deal with the DA's office.
文件已经放他桌子上了 只需要一点点助力
He's got the paper on his desk. Case needs a little shove.
而且连任选举在即 那些混蛋急需用钱
And reelection's around the corner. Those fuckers need money.
现在正在分配合同
Contracts are being gifted out,
大部分都在你的掌控之下
most of them under your umbrella.
我需要有人引起他的注意
I need someone to get his attention,
把文件摊在他眼皮子底下
to put this paper under his fucking nose
让他赶紧签字
and make him fuckin' sign it.
要是我自己可以的话 我早就一脚踹开他的门
If I could, I'd kick open the fucking door
把事情办妥了
and get done myself.
可以
Okay.
好的
NEW字幕组翻译
翻译  炭炭
翻译  无敌小康康
翻译  Melody
翻译  江湖
校对  头上长仙草
校对  千阳
时间轴  长颂
时间轴  阿渊
啦啦队  千阳
总监  千阳
CSEG克隆字幕提取组
提取  Caliro
@CSEG克隆字幕提取组
《金斯敦市长》
第二季 第六集
本字幕由CSEG克隆字幕提取组提取分享  仅供学习交流之用  禁止压制  禁止删除字幕组及CSEG署名
禁止分享食物
欢迎关注新浪微博、微信公众号：CSEG克隆字幕提取组
你是说把邦尼单独监禁不算大问题
So you telling me Bunny in the hole ain't a fucking problem?
邦尼中午就能出来
Bunny'll be out by noon.
而且都已经把他关起来了
Besides, even in that hole,
那些蠢蛋还在搞小动作
motherfucker still making moves.
到处都能闻到那些狗杂种
Still smell that crispy, bitch-ass motherfucker
身上的骚味
in the air.
都是雅利安兄弟会搞的鬼
That was AB sanctioning shit.
他们收买了狱警 兄弟
They got the guards, bro.
得狱警者得监狱
As long as you got the guards, you got the yard.
是啊 不过平衡要被打破了
Yeah, well, that balance about to shift.
你怎么知道
How you see that?
听着拉夫 我必须有份
I gotta earn, Raph.
你得有付出才能有收获
You gotta be slinging in to be earning out.
懂我意思吗
Know what I'm saying?
等邦尼出去之后 不管他会不会
When Bunny get out, no matter if he gotta
亲自收拾那个白佬 坏事都会发生
drop that cracker hisself, shit's going down.
我们会夺回我们的东西
We gettin' our shit back.
我不这么看 兄弟
I don't see it, bro.
那是因为你就剩一只眼了
That's cause you got one fucking eye.
我开玩笑的 老兄
Man, I'm fucking with you, man.
出牌吧
Play your card.
喂 拉夫
Yo, Raph.
到我了是吗
Oh, it's on me, huh?
我不懂为什么你们几个这么想输
I didn't know you motherfuckers were so eager to lose.
我们今天可不会输
We ain't losing today.
是吗 我们走着瞧
Shit, we'll see about that.
你他妈的还出方块
Fuck you still doin' with a diamond?
会不会打啊傻逼
Reneggin'-ass bitch.
好了 别喊 他还在学怎么打
Yo, hold up, Hush. Kid's still learnin'.
那让他上桌干什么 老D
Then why is he at the fucking table, D?
我们三缺一啊
Y'all needed a fourth.
你们觉得邦会把那个白猪干掉吗
You think Bun gonna take out a pig or what?
要出事了
Shit's about to pop.
那可不 那些混蛋还欠咱们...
No shit. Motherfuckers owe us--
刀片
Blade!
操
Shit.
带走
Go!
-谢了 丽贝卡  -不客气
- Thank you, Rebecca. - You're welcome.
谢谢你回我电话
Hey, thanks for calling me back.
他今天晚上应该就能出来了
He should be out by the end of the day.
应该能
He should be?
一开始就不该把他关到单人牢房
Never should have been in AdSeg in the first place,
他可是你的犯人
he's your inmate.
这监狱又不是我的
I don't run this prison,
我只能监视金斯敦的犯人
I just oversee inmates from Kingstown.
赶紧把他放出来 好吧
Just get him out,
他可没法在小盒子间里管事
all right, he can't run shit from inside that box.
把他放回普通牢房
Put him in general pop.
有个很受尊敬的墨西哥人可能会反对
There's a toasted Mexican who I think would beg to differ.
这事跟邦尼无关好吗
Well, that wasn't Bunny. Okay?
是雅利安兄弟会在搞事
That was AB makin' a play.
你也知道的
And you know it.
他们想减少棕色或黑色人种的数量
Want to reduce the numbers of browns or blacks.
这就是我想说的 麦克
That's my point, Mike.
锚湾是雅利安兄弟会的地盘
Anchor Bay is AB.
半数狱警都是加入或支持
Half them COs in here are Aryan affiliated
雅利安兄弟会的雅利安人
or sympathetic to the cause.
我只在这待几天
I'm only here for a few days
交接下文件 做做例行检查
pushing paper, doing checks.
在我搞清楚背后的操纵者之前 我真的无能为力
I can't do shit until I find out who's pulling the strings here.
行行行 好吧 很好
Yeah, okay. Okay, great.
听着 那我就亲自进去一趟
Look, I'm just gonna go in myself.
可以吗 能给我批个访问者身份吗
How's that? Can you give me visitors?
这点事至少能办到吧
Can you do that, at least?
能
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
操
Fuck.
怎么了
What's going on?
嘿 宝贝
Hey babe!
-宝贝  -怎么了
- Baby. - Huh?
你妈妈需要个货棚还是怎么了
Did your mom need a shed or...
我不知道 可能吧 对吧 我...
Uh, I don't know. Probably. Right? I mean...
我去商场时看到了 当时我就想
I went to the store and I saw it and I thought to myself,
这地方给她放园艺用品之类的
you know, that would be a good place for her to put her
放些杂物正合适 所以我就搭了
gardening stuff and shit. And so I built it,
-还有两个没搭呢  -是呢
- and I got two more. - Right.
唐家餐馆
他说出什么事了吗
Did he say what it was about?
听起来一团糟 我就知道这些
Sounded like shit, that's all I know.
他让我给你和凯尔打电话
He said call you, call Kyle.
过来碰面
Said come down here and meet.
-就说了这些 没别的了  -不 伊恩
- That's all, that was it?. - No, Ian.
他还说了什么狗屁生活的意义
He told me the fucking meaning of life,
我只是不想跟你分享
I just don't wanna share it with you.
怪了 像是我说的话
Strange, that's all I'm saying.
唐娜 你们这有什么派吗
Hey, Donna. What kinda pie you got?
有香蕉奶油和山核桃的
Banana cream and pecan.
是都在一个派里吗
Like, in one pie?
不是 是两种派 两种不同馅料
No, it's two pies. It's two different kinds of pie.
卡里姆
狱警叫戴维森 明早九点安排你和邦尼见面
刚出炉的吗
- Are they fresh? - Meh...
-唐娜 来杯啤酒吧  -没问题
- Donna, can I get a beer? - Sure thing.
也给我来份派
Gimme a piece of pie, too.
哪种
Which?
哪个都行 给我个惊喜
I don't care. Surprise me.
还是各来一个吧
Both of 'em, one each.
天啊 不是吧 别管派了 他人都来了
Christ. Really? Stop with the pie, he's here.
怎么了 你叫凯尔了吗
- What's going on? - Did you call Kyle?
叫了 在来的路上了
Yeah, He's on his way.
好 我等会儿
Yeah, I'll wait.
我等不了 虽然我很想
I can't, as much as I'd like to
一直看着这位小丑吃派
watch this clown eat pie all day.
行了吧 吃一口保准你爱上
Come on, you'll love it.
我还要去锚湾 或者什么鬼地方
Gotta get over to Anchor and wherever else.
到底怎么了
What's going on?
-我收到了举报信  -真操蛋
- I got a heart attack letter. - Holy fuck.
-什么时候  -今天早上
- When? - This morning.
地检说该请个律师了
DA said it's time to lawyer up,
把我这摊子烂事处理好
get my shit in order and everything.
-操  -嘿
- Shit. - Hey.
发生什么事了
What's up?
怎么了 有什么大事儿吗
What's the big deal?
举报信
Heart attack letter.
操
Oh, fuck.
是啊 他们就是冲我来的
Yeah, they're coming for me.
没错 你知道是谁吗
Yeah. You know who?
地检 不然呢
DA, what do you think?
不 我是说 谁出卖了你
No, I mean, who's rollin'?
什么意思
What do you mean?
他们不会因为犯人的证词来找你
They ain't comin' after you because of inmate testimony.
好吧 应该是自己人
Okay? Somebody rolled.
你要点什么吗 亲
You want something, hon?
不 不用了
No.
让我们单独聊会儿 好吧 唐娜
Just give us a second, would ya, Donna?
谢了 唐娜 非常感谢
Thanks, Donna. I appreciate it.
我们不需要什么了
We're all good.
你觉得是谁
Who you thinking?
我们他妈的都是一家人啊 麦克
We're a fucking family, Mike,
没人会背叛自己人
nobody in there's rolling on anybody.
有人会的
Somebody did.
这是正当防卫 麦克
It was self-defense, Mike.
当时可是有几百号人在里面
I mean, there were hundreds of them in there.
我们可能会被生吞活剥的
You know, we would have gotten torn apart.
正当防卫
Self-defense.
该死 他们应该跪舔我的
Bullshit, they should be suckin' my dick,
不给我来个表彰游行都说不过去
throwin' me a goddamn parade.
我们在里面就把这破事解决了
We stopped that fucking thing from the inside.
听着 我知道 也理解你
Look, I hear you, I get it.
但他们想杀鸡儆猴
But they want a pound,
而且明显想拿你开刀
and apparently wanna take it from you.
那国民警卫队那群混蛋呢
What about those National Guard assholes?
那群傻逼现在在监狱围墙上打着游戏
I mean, those fucking idiots are playing video games
啥也不管
up on those walls.
我不知道 这无关紧要 罗伯特
Doesn't matter, Robert,
这是他们的事
they have something.
既然你们说不是你们的人
And if you say it's not one of your guys,
我就相信你们 但我还是觉得 是你们的人干的
I gotta believe you, but I got my money on one of these guys.
自己良心上过不去了 或者跟地检做了一笔交易
Got a crisis of conscience or sweet deal with the DA,
大差不差
something like that.
我也多留意 看看能不能发现什么
I'll look around, see what I can dig up.
那我们还要做什么
So what we do in the meantime?
把你们那套说辞捋清楚了
Get your story straight.
好吗
Okay?
好
Yeah.
之后有事吗
Doing anything after this?
-我吗 没有 怎么了  -有个事儿
- Me?  No, why? - Got an errand.
我可以让你加入进来 让你练习练习
I can get you on the books. Get you some baby scratch.
行 没问题
Yeah, sure.
我们应该再聊聊这个事
We should talk this shit through.
好 好
Yeah. Yeah.
你今晚有事吗
What are you doing tonight?
今晚 今晚 特蕾西今晚要工作 所以...
Tonight? Tonight. Tracy's working tonight, so...
-九点 我去找你  -好
- 9:00. I'm going to be there. - Okay.
你找到这个人 好吗
You find this guy, all right?
找到他 问题就解决了 对吗 麦克
You find him, and we will be fine, right Mike?
好 找到是谁在乱说
Yeah. Yeah. Just find out who's talking,
我们再采取下一步行动 解决这个事儿 好吧
and then we'll take the next steps to take care of it, okay?
-好  -不用担心
- Yeah. - Don't worry about it.
还有 不要跟任何人
In the meantime, just don't say anything to anybody
说这件事 好吗
about this shit, okay?
振作起来 不会有事的
Keep your chin up. We're all good.
-走吧  -没问题
- Let's get the fuck out of here. - 100 percent.
-真操蛋啊 对吧  -是啊 太他妈糟心了
- This is fucked up, right? - Yeah, it's fucked up.
等一下 我去拿个东西
Hey, hold on. Give me a second, huh?
丽贝卡 帮我查个地址
Hey, Rebecca, I need an address.
好吗 我只有一个姓 戴维森
Okay? All I got is the last name, Davidson,
他是锚湾的狱警
He's a guard over at Anchor Bay.
找到了就发短信给我 好吧
All right, well just--just text it to me when you get it, okay?
拜 谢了
Bye, thank you.
这他妈是啥
The fuck is that?
你们不是一直在说这个 我拿到了
There's too much talk about it. I grabbed 'em.
东西是杰瑞在看管 他给了我五分钟
Fucking Jerry in the lockup. He gave me 5 minutes,
美国摇滚乐队
我给了他莫莉·哈切特的演唱会门票
got him tickets to the Molly Hatchet concert.
对 没问题的
Yeah. Yeah, we're good.
老天爷
Christ.
去他妈的举报信 是吧
Fucking heart attack letter, huh?
-是啊  -天啊
- Yeah. - Geez.
你的地检朋友没跟你说什么吗
Your DA friend didn't wanna tell you?
说的话太多了 凯尔
People say a lot of things, Kyle.
很难分清哪些话是真的
It's hard to tell when they mean it.
是啊
Yeah.
你不能再冒险干这种事了 知道了吗
You can't be going off and doing shit. Okay?
什么 什么意思
What? What do you mean?
就是那些债券啊 你以为我说的是什么
I mean the fucking bonds. The fuck you think I mean?
你不能这样不跟我和史蒂夫说一声
You can't go walking in to fucking lockup.
就大摇大摆地进去偷东西 好吗
without tellin' me or Stevie or somebody, all right?
-那有监控  -麦克 我在金斯敦警局干过
- They got cameras in there. - Mike! I was KPD.
里面什么样我清楚得很 硬盘都删干净了
I know where everything is in there. I wiped the drives.
不用担心 没事的
Don't worry, we're good.
这样看起来岂不是更可疑了吗
And you don't think it looks suspicious?
就算很可疑 谁他妈在意啊
Who gives a fuck if it looks suspicious?
只要找不到我们头上 不是吗
As long as it doesn't come back on us. Right?
我只有一个要求 做事不要越界
Just stay inside the lines, that's all I'm askin'.
你不能越界 顶多越一点儿 明白吗
Stay inside lines, just a little bit. All right?
等这阵风头过去 你也冷静一下
Let the world settle down. You settle down.
兰博是《第一滴血》的主角 电影讲述了退伍军人兰博
在小镇上屡受警长的欺凌逼得他逃入山林被迫对警察展开反击的故事
不要再装兰博了 天啊 你肩上有很多担子的
No more Rambo shit. Jesus, you got a lot going on.
是啊
Yeah...
你觉得我会是个好爸爸吗
Do you think I'm going to be a good dad?
什么意思 你当然会是了
What do you mean? Yeah, of course.
把孩子带到这个世界上
I mean, bringing the kid into this world,
在这个城市里抚养长大也算吗
raising them in this town?
确实 这城市很烂
Yeah, that's fucked up.
但至少你不是烂人
At least you're not.
你一定会是个绝世好爸爸
You're gonna be fucking great.
我们要干嘛
What are we doing?
在这儿停一下
Gotta make a stop.
天啊
Aw, Jesus.
如果我五分钟内没回来 明白吗
If I'm not back in 5 minutes. All right?
五分钟
Five minutes.
什么鬼啊
The fuck?
你是戴维森吗
Hey, you Davidson?
看情况 你要卖我东西 还是给我看逮捕令
Depends. You sellin' something, or servin' me papers?
都不是 我是麦克·麦克拉斯基
Naw, Mike McLusky.
聊一会儿可以吗
Talk to you for a minute?
太行了
Ah, fucking A.
兄弟 进来吧
Yeah, brother. Come on in.
我这地方乱糟糟的
Yeah, I mean, the place is kind of a mess.
把这地方给你腾出来
Get this out of your way here.
给你拿瓶啤酒还是什么
Get you a beer or something?
不用了
Nah, I'm good.
坐吧 兄弟
Have a seat, brother.
这样就行 就待一会儿
Nah, I'm good. Just be here for a minute.
我听说
So look, I hear, um,
你在锚湾话语权很大
you're the big shit over at Anchor.
能这么说吧
Some say.
行 我需要你别招惹邦尼·华盛顿了
Okay, I need you back off Bunny Washington.
我做不到 麦克
I can't do that, Mike.
我可不是在请求你
I wasn't really asking.
你是在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
监狱里的局势有种很微妙的平衡
It's just a delicate balance going on over there.
但你偏向于雅利安兄弟会那边
And you pushing the scale to AB
那只会给我添麻烦
is not really helping me here.
你知道
You know,
我们那原本有自己的平衡
we had our own balance in there.
是
Yeah.
咱们这是要干嘛
The fuck are we doing?
你觉得呢 麦克
What's it look like, Mike?
我不是来找你打架的
I'm not here to fight you.
我来这只是出于礼节
I came here as a courtesy,
告诉你一声 不管你配不配合
tell you that this is going to happen
事都得这么办
with or without your cooperation.
所以...
So...
你他妈的给我滚出去
Get the fuck out of my house.
操
Fuck.
-嘿 退后  -我操 好吧
- Hey, back up! - What the fuck? All right!
-放轻松  -你他妈的退后
- Relax! - Back the fuck up!
放松 凯尔
Relax, Kyle...
你再敢动我哥一下 混蛋
Think you can lay a hand on my brother, motherfucker?
我就把你丫的脑浆都他妈打出来
I will paint the walls with your goddamn brains.
听好 白痴 照我说的做 好吧
Look, dickhead, just do what I fucking say, all right?
别他妈搞小动作 知道吗
And don't do fucking anything, all right?
别招惹邦尼 这他妈没那么难做到
Don't fuck with Bunny. It's not that fucking hard.
如果你搞了私下交易
You know, you're gettin' something on the side,
好处可能会变少
maybe get a little bit less.
-嘿 嘿 嘿  -知道了
- Hey. Hey, hey. - All right!
你要是敢不听话 我就回来找你
You fuck around. I'm going to come back here.
把你的世界都毁了 明白吗
And I'm gonna ruin your world. You understand?
邦尼明早转回到普通牢房 没得商量
Bunny wakes up in gen pop, period.
别招惹邦尼
Don't fuck with Bunny.
咱们走
Let's go.
我还以为你跟我们是一拨的 麦克
Thought you were one of us, Mike.
你丫以为错了
You thought fucking wrong.
-走吧  -看着我
- Let's go. - Hey, look at me.
看着我 照他说的做就行
Look at me, just do what he says.
-行了 凯尔  -操
Fuck it Kyle.
咱们走
Let's go.
我他妈怎么跟你说的
What the fuck did I tell you? What are you doing?
-你闹哪样  -我从窗户里看到你们了
I was looking through the window.
神他妈的窗户
The fucking window?
对啊 你说的五分钟
Yeah, you said 5 minutes.
这他妈不到五分钟 混蛋
That wasn't fucking 5 minutes, motherfucker.
我觉得到五分钟了
Well, it felt like 5 minutes.
根本他妈的没到
Well, it's fucking wasn't.
就会拿枪揍人的混蛋
Pistol whippin' motherfuckers.
-得他妈给你买块表  -真的觉得到五分钟了
- Buy you a fucking watch! - It felt like 5 minutes.
妈
Ma?
我们在这边
Yeah, we're in here!
-嗨  -嗨 哦
- Hey. - Hey. Oh.
我忘了
I forgot.
额...真是...
You know, um...
抱歉让你们等我到这么晚
Sorry for keeping you up.
我能跟你说句话吗
Could I talk to you for a minute?
咱们不是正说着话呢吗
I thought we were talking.
去厨房里 我跟他很快就说完
In the kitchen. I won't keep him a minute.
不着急 您随意
Take your time. Take your time.
-我没事 妈  -好吧 好吧
- Everything's fine, Mom. - Yeah. Okay. All right.
你今天是跟麦克一起干活了吗
And did you work with Michael today?
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
感觉如何
How was that?
挺好的 一切都挺好的
It was good. Good. Yeah, everything's good.
-好  -只是要跟伊恩商量金斯敦警局的事
- Good. - Just trying to figure out this KPD thing with Ian.
-是吧  -所以 你知道 但一切都很好
- Right? - So I just, you know. But everything's good. Yeah.
-好吧  -你还好吗
- Okay. - You good?
我 还好
Me? Yeah, well...
还行 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
-就这事吗 因为我  -对
- Is that it? 'Cause I just-- - Yeah. Oh, yeah.
去吧 去吧宝贝
Go, go honey. Go.
一切都很好
No, everything's fine.
-好的 谢谢  -晚安
- Okay, thanks. - Goodnight.
早就他妈的该把爷放出去了
It's about motherfuckin' time.
等我处理完你们这些混蛋 我要称霸这个监狱
I'ma own this prison by the time I'm done with you motherfuckers.
你脚镣叮当响 听着可不像能称霸监狱的人
Well, that shackle shuffle says something else to me, but
但要保有希望 邦
keep hope alive, Bun.
这跟希望无关 卡尼
It ain't about hope no more, Carney.
这就是掌控和掌管的区别
That's the difference between taking control and taking charge.
我知道这里的局面是我掌控不了的
And I know I ain't in control of this shit no more.
但我他妈一定要掌管这个监狱
But I sure as fuck will take charge up in this bitch.
囚犯
惩戒所
访客
好了 谢谢
All right, thanks.
邦尼
Bunny.
今天就转移出去
Makin' the move today.
要是米契的话 事早都办成了
Mitch'd already made that move.
是啊 但我不是米契
Yeah, well, I'm not Mitch.
没错 你不是他
No, you ain't.
过去这些天没有开车扫射事件
There's been, um, no drive-bys the last few days.
没有大屠杀 没有无辜的人遇害
No mass murders, no innocent people being killed.
肯定有什么事是做对了
Something must be going right.
你告诉我
Answer me this.
我应该允许你搞我多少次
How many times I'm supposed to let you fuck me?
我告诉你在里面要低调
I told you to keep it quiet inside here.
你他妈怎么做的
What the fuck did you do?
你他妈把墨西哥帮的首领给点着了
You torched the fucking Mexican gatekeeper.
这事不是很低调吧 对吗
That's not exactly keepin' it quiet, is it?
这里没法低调 麦克
Quiet ain't a thing in here, Mike.
低调也许能保你一时的安稳
Quiet maybe keep you clean for a minute,
但迟早会有混蛋过来找你麻烦
but sooner or later, some mottherfucker gonna hit you with a question.
所以你最好准备好一个响亮的回应 麦克
So you better be ready with a loud-ass motherfucking answer, Mike!
你帮不上我 那么我得自己高调起来
You ain't doing for me. So I gotta raise my voice now.
我有个新的角度 好吗 而且我正从各个方面着手解决
I have a new angle. Okay? And I'm hitting on all sides.
所以你在这里很安全 明白吗
So you're good in here. You understand?
你很快就能被放出去 我告诉你
You're gonna be out in minutes, I'm telling you.
听着 麦克 我受够了听人安排
Look, Mike, I'm tired of being told.
知道吗
All right?
我受够了被人牵着鼻子走
I'm tired of being the dog dragged by the wagon.
我不会再躺平任人摆布了
I ain't layin' down and gettin' dragged along no more.
不 我要亲手掌握局面
No, I'm taking this shit into my own hands now.
-拜托 求你了  -别再拜托了 哥们
- Come on, please. - No more please, man.
本来有人要做掉你 你知道吗
There was a mark on you. You know that?
我看在过去的交情上帮你把危险转移了
I move that shit, I moved that shit outta history with you.
你转移了 邦尼 转给谁了
You moved it? Bunny, to who?
你他妈给转移到哪去了
Where the fuck did you move it?
你别操心了 麦克
Don't worry about it, Mike.
你只管继续牵线搭桥
You just keep pulling your strings.
把我弄出去 我就会试着扫清障碍
Get me out of here. I'll try to clear the way.
帮我就是帮你自己 麦克老兄
Help me help you, brother Mike.
现在谁有危险 邦尼
Who's wearing it, Bunny?
知道的人会知道
That's need to know shit.
你丫不需要知道
Yo ass don't need to.
不管你在做什么 停手
Whatever it is you're doing, don't.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
金斯敦少年犯感化中心
谢谢
Thank you.
其他人都在院子里
The rest are in the yard.
-先生 你能把他的手铐打开吗  -不行 女士
- Um, Sir. Can you uncuff him? - No, ma'am.
我猜你必须得留在这个房间里
I'm guessing you're required to stay in the room.
是的 女士 除非您是他的律师
Yes, ma'am. Unless you're his attorney,
那么您就能有特权
in which case you have the privilege.
我不是 多谢了
Oh, no. Well, I'm not. So, thanks.
你好 雅各布
Hello, Jacob.
你好
Hello.
你有话想跟我说是吗
You wanted to talk to me?
我...
I've been...
我在这日子很不好过
I've been having a pretty crappy time right here.
我现在18岁了 我的律师给我争取到一个协议
Uh, I'm 18 now. My lawyer, he got me a deal.
我只需要保证一年不犯事
I just--I just have to go a year without incident.
但假如我搞砸了 犯了事
But if I mess up or anything,
我的刑期就变为八年 并且要转监到州立监狱
my--my sentence goes eight and state.
天哪 你可千万别搞砸
Oh, man, you don't want to mess up.
是啊
Yeah.
上周白佬来找我
Uh, the Woods came to me last week.
-白佬  -那些白人
- The Woods? - The white boys.
我如果不加入他们 我就是一个人
If I don't join up with them, I'm--I'm going to be all alone.
如果只有我一个人 我根本都没机会能活过一年
And if I'm all alone, I won't have a chance of making it a year.
我觉得我不...我理解你的处境...
I don't think I-- I understand...
我知道...我知道你的儿子是什么人物
I know--I know who your son is.
麦克·麦克拉斯基 那就是你儿子 对不对
And Mike McLusky. That's your son, right?
是他 没错
Yeah, mm-hmm.
他是内部的人 对吧 他跟兄弟会是一起的
He was inside, right? He was with the Brotherhood.
不是吗
Wasn't he?
我只能说 我想他只是为了活下去 不得不用尽各种手段
Well, I mean, I guess he did everything he had to do to survive.
那好
Right.
我是这么想的 你看
I thought that, you know,
我要是没办法离这帮人远点的话
I'm gonna--I'm gonna mess this up if I can't stay away
最后我肯定会搞砸这一切的
from these people and all.
我想着 要是可以的话
I thought that maybe,
如果你能帮忙 跟你儿子提一句
maybe you could, you could speak to your son.
然后要是他愿意的话 他可以帮我一把
Or, maybe he can, he could help me.
就是说他...他可以帮我对付那些人
You know, he-- he could help me with them.
或者能帮我换个地方
Or he could help me get moved.
我只是不想...
I just don't--
我就是想着 也许你能帮我跟你儿子说一下我的事
I just hope that maybe you could speak to your son for me.
我会的
I will.
我会跟他说的
I will speak to him.
代客泊车 卡塞斯餐厅 服务费十美元
喂 你好吗 我是麦克·麦克拉斯基
Hey, hey. How you doing? Mike McLusky.
很高兴见到你 麦克
Nice to meet you, Mike.
麦克 你怎么知道我在这儿
Mike? How'd you find me?
丽贝卡和你的助理的口风 可太严实了
Rebecca and your assistant are, you know, tight.
其实我就是想占用你们一小会儿时间
Yeah, I just want to take a minute of your time to, um,
-商量一下我们的安排  -现在不合适 麦克
- talk about our arrangement. - Yeah. Not now, Mike.
你指的是哪些安排
What arrangement is that?
是这样 你跟我认识的人做了笔交易
Well, you did a deal with people I know.
我们让你的街区恢复了平静
We got you peace in the streets.
也让你在媒体面前可以大吹特吹
Got you peacocking in front of the press.
所以我看差不多也该让你这边把交易收尾
So I think it's about time you held up your end of the deal
然后把那些人都给他妈给我放出来
and sign them the fuck out.
你想的挺美哈
You think that. Huh?
废他妈的话
Fuck yeah I do.
我跟我在沃里克集团的朋友聊过几句
Talked to my friend over at Warwick.
我知道眼下的情况
I understand that
市里现在正在商讨一些要事
there's a major negotiation within the city happening,
重新选举也迫在眉睫
and with a reelection coming up,
-麦克...  -怎么了
- Mike... - What?
-拜托  -首先
- Please. - First of all, your friends
你在沃里克集团的朋友如果要跟我作对 他们失去的东西
at Warwick have a lot more to lose by crossing me
可要比跟你合作挣到的好处多得多
than they have to gain by supporting you.
其次 你现在帮着出头的这些人
And second of all, these people you're advocating for
可都是危险的罪犯
are dangerous criminals.
他们都是因为对社会产生了威胁 所以才会被逮捕
They were arrested because they present a menace to society.
我凭什么把他们放出来
Now, why would I release them?
因为这他妈是你跟他们约定好的 就凭这个
Because you made a fucking deal with them. That's why.
事情可以商量 自然也就可以违约 麦克拉斯基先生
Deals are made and broken all the time, Mr. McLusky.
握手和口头商定也好 写在纸面上也罢 这都不重要
Hand shakes, verbal, paper. None of it matters.
这你妈当然很重要 对他们都很重要
It fucking matters. Matters to them.
这个交易是他们所有的依靠 理应一诺千金
Deal's all they got, word is bond.
真有意思 那句话怎么说来着
Interesting. Whatever happened to, uh,
一群做贼的 当了婊子还想立牌坊
no honor among thieves, huh?
你跟他提过麦洛·森特的事情了吗
You tell him about Milo Sunter?
麦洛·森特已经死了
Milo Sunter's dead.
有可能吧
Yeah. Maybe.
但他更有可能正在你这个操蛋城市的街巷里
Or more likely just walking around the streets
到处游荡 因为那个替死鬼
of your fucking city with no DNA
什么DNA之类的信息都查不到
or anything on the records of the dead.
要是你能把你许下的这些傻逼诺言兑现
Now, if you hold up to your fucking end of the deal,
我可以帮你想想办法 引诱他上钩
I can give you something to bait the hook.
暴露他的行踪
Can flush him out.
或者我也可以去找那些狗逼媒体
Or I'll just go to the fucking press
告诉他们说你知道麦洛逍遥法外
and tell 'em you knew Milo escaped
-而且还他妈袖手旁观  -那是惩戒所的事 与我无关
- and did fuck all about it. - That's DOC. It's not on me.
你觉得你的选民能知道这里头的猫腻吗
Do you think your voters know the difference?
你才是露脸的
You're the face.
-我不知道这事  -你不知道
- I didn't know. - You didn't?
地方助理检察官都知道
Assistant DA knew.
没有人会相信你对这事一无所知
No one's gonna believe that you didn't.
那就说定了 我们把这事儿解决
All right, let's get it done.
很高兴见到你 伊芙琳
Good to see you, Evelyn.
你有空吗
You got a second?
什么事
What's up?
这是什么
What's this?
我需要你签个字
I need your signature.
我们那个帐篷城的朋友死了
Our friend from Tent City died.
你说什么
What?
就今天早上的事
Today. This morning.
你以为我们
You think we can
把这事儿糊弄过去就完了
just sweep this under the rug?
上面已经改成了以前的日期
It's backdated.
我们的屁股也擦干净了
Our asses are covered.
写的是犯人们卷进了一场无差别的斗殴
Inmates were involved in a mutual combat.
他被人发现失去知觉 之后立即送医
He was found unresponsive and tended to immediately.
还是平时那一套 谁也没看到什么可疑的事
Usual story. No one saw anything.
这下他再也没法开口放屁了
He sure ain't fucking talking.
他们会查看他在医务室的就医记录
They will see his infirmary records.
后续有没有跟进他的健康状况
Did he have follow-up care?
他不想抱怨身上的伤痛
Didn't want to complain about the pain.
因为他不想被人当成一个死娘炮
Didn't want to be seen as a pussy.
文件就留我这儿吧
Leave it here.
这他妈也太凶残了
Shit is brutal.
我听说他们找了几个傻逼去挖坟还是什么的
I heard they got motherfuckers digging graves or some shit.
这种逼事根本就是狗草的奴隶劳动
Fucking slave labor. That's what this shit is.
这是正经事
This big business.
这些事都是正经事
That's what this shit is.
外边料理好了没有
Shit gettin' done on the outside?
他们说是弄好了 老哥
That's what they say, cuzzo.
这老逼坦子又要搞什么飞机
Fuck this hayseed doing?
我没有恶意 兄弟
No bad intentions, brother.
我可不是你的兄弟
I ain't your brother.
有屁快放 你他妈到底想说啥
Well, spit it. The fuck you want?
搞你的那个杂种是擅自行动
That bitch jumped at you wasn't sanctioned.
他喜欢搞"独行侠"那套 结果给自己招来了危险
Guy was a lone wolf and earned himself a green light.
当时码头上不止你一个人
Wasn't just you on that pier.
如果你想加快这事的进度 我们有资源
If you're makin' moves to speed things up, we got resources.
我就说一声
I'm just saying.
狱警
Hey CO!
这个托盘搬运车歇逼了
This pallet jack is fucked.
你看看这坨废铁...
Look at this shit...
这傻逼老坦子跟这儿装什么好人
Fucking peckerwoods bein' so friendly for?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只知道我们得赶紧离开这个鬼地方
I know we gotta get the fuck up outta here.
我操
Fuck.
这下手也他妈太狠了
Bitch ass.
妈的 不
Oh, fuck no!
还好吗
What's up?
我就过来瞅一眼 都还顺利吗
Just checking in. We doin' good?
-一切正常 哥  -好 美发沙龙那里如何
- All good, G. - Yeah. What about the salon?
这附近现在连交头接耳的人都没了
Nobody even whispering around this way no more.
感觉好像又回到以前的样子了
Shit's feeling like shit again.
跟我来
Come on.
好安静啊
That's quiet.
是啊
Yeah.
城堡巍然不动 只待王者归来
Castle's intact. Just needs its king back.
我是麦克
Yeah, it's Mike.
接通此通话需付费 拨叫人是
This is a collect call from...
邦尼·华盛顿
Bunny Washington.
拨叫地点是锚湾惩戒中心
At the Anchor Bay Correctional facility.
话费标准 2.4美元可通话15分钟 确认接通请按1
To accept the charge of $2.40 for 15 minutes, press 1,
拒接请按...您可以开始通话了
to refuse press-- You may begin your call now.
-喂 邦尼  -我时间不多 好吗
- Hey, Bunny. - I ain't got long. Aight?
我就是想跟你说一声
I just want to let you know
路子已经都清理干净了
that the path's been cleared and shit.
行吧 你该做你的事了
Okay? Time for you to do your thing.
本字幕由CSEG克隆字幕提取组提取分享  仅供学习交流之用  禁止压制  禁止删除字幕组及CSEG署名
我的什么事
What thing?
你这市长不能白当啊 大哥 把我从这地方弄出去 麦克
Your mayor thing, man. Get me outta this place, Mike.
你说什么路子清理干净了 邦尼
What path's been cleared, Bunny?
我这边的破事都做好了 现在轮到你了
I did my shit, now it's your turn.
字幕错漏、合作联系、加入我们，请发送邮件至：csegkelongzimutiquzu@gmail.com
叫你那边那个贱种把文件签了
Get that bitch of yours to sign the papers
然后赶紧送老子回家
and send my black ass home.
回来再联络 麦克市长
Catch you later, Mayor Mike.
欢迎关注新浪微博、微信公众号：CSEG克隆字幕提取组